Hello everyone, this is Haruka Koizumi, aka Oharu.
Yes, today.
A while ago, in the video commentary on "The Selfish Princess,
I thought you might like to know how everyone feels about love.
I wanted to know how you feel about love, so I asked you how you feel about love.
And that's what I've decided to share with you today.
This is my favorite.
Can you see it? This is Compota.
I'm going to answer your question over a Compota.
Let's get started!
Let's go!
So, I asked you all how you feel about love.
When I was explaining the gaga pudding
I asked about everyone's sense of love.
I don't know why you wanted to know.
I don't know... it was something about heavy girlfriends...
I think that's what happened.
I was updating a lot of stories yesterday, so...
Oh, this is it!
Okay!
I'll read it then.
Okay, and I've got some compotas.
I'll be sipping a little bit of compota as I go.
I really like Compota.
I've already had about 3 or 4 glasses of compota.
I've already had about 3 or 4 glasses of it.
I drank 3 or 4 drinks from a vending machine....
Mmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmm
Mmmmmm...
Yuck!
Oh, shit.
Okay, here we go.
Uh-huh? Hmm? Okay, here we go.
Someone fun to be with.
Someone who shares the same sense of money and so on.
Yes, that's important.
Someone who is fun to be with.
Financial sense is also important.
Someone who keeps in touch with me frequently.
I understand this a lot.
Cleanliness is good. Cleanliness is good.
Cleanliness is good.
Cleanliness is good, cleanliness is good.
Eh... my preference is for someone with thin lines, but if I'm going to marry someone chubby, I like chubby.
I didn't know that was a thing.
Hmm... yeah.
Someone who's a good cook.
Missed.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
He's a good cook.
Isn't he great?
Someone who usually relies on me and is a spoiled brat
But when there's an emergency, he's always there to help.
Usually depends on me and is a spoiled brat.
I see.
He's the type of guy who makes you feel like you're the odd man out.
Someone who's funny.
That's important.
He seems quiet and cool, but he's funny and fun.
I'm a sucker for gaps in a guy's personality.
She's cute... she's getting cute... she seems cool, but she's funny and fun... she's vulnerable to gaps in a guy's personality.
He's cute.
He's getting cute.
I want a guy who can get rid of bugs when they appear.
I know.
When I get a bug, I definitely call my dad.
I'd say, "Daddy, it's a bug!
It's all about consideration, isn't it?
I like someone who is considerate and kind.
Someone who sees the best in you.
That's right.
Someone who tells me I'm doing my best.
I also like someone who tells me I'm doing my best.
I don't...
I don't want my hobbies interfered with.
Of course.
Because it's my hobby.
So I'd like someone who prioritizes my hobbies.
Or, if it were me, someone who would recognize that I'm trying to achieve my dream.
Someone who would tell me I'm doing my best.
Someone who eats pointy corn on his fingers.People who eat corn on the cob with their fingers.
What do you mean? What do you mean? What do you mean?
Someone who supports me in my quest to reach my dreams.
It's important to have someone who encourages you to follow your dreams.
Wait a minute, this... this... this...
Jjorka gave me this recently.
This is a phone stand.
I'm gonna use this one for a second because it's more convenient for me.
It's just perfect.
It's just right.
It's perfect!
That's so perfect!
It's fun to talk to you, of course.
Ah!
Of course it's fun to talk.
People who don't have a hard time in silence not talking.
You know what I mean? You know what I mean?
Like at Disney.
I know, but there are definitely times of silence.
Even with my best friend, there are moments of silence.
But when I'm with my best friend, it's not awkward at all.
That's really important.
It's all about feeling.
Who wants to say "feeling"?
I like a kind girl with a nice smile.
Yes!
Thank you for saying this, but I've been waiting for it for a while.
Type of person of the opposite sex
Someone who works hard.
Especially for someone else.
That's why I married my wife.
Wow.
That's a throwback.
Wow, that's cool.
That's cool.
Yeah. - Yeah.
Eh, someone who has good taste in food, because I like to eat.
Wow, that's cool.
I like to eat.
And the best is someone like Oharu-chan.
teehee
what's that, why, eh, what's wrong?
Ha-ha-ha-ha
If I'm going to get married, it should definitely be someone I can talk things over with.
Also, someone who is kind to parents and family.
Parents and family.
And also, a waiter at a convenience store.
That kind of thing is pretty important.
When you go to a convenience store and they put something in a bag
For putting something in a bag at a convenience store
Thank you for putting the bag in the convenience store.
That kind of thing is really important.
The person you like is your type.
You know...
You've been saying this for a long time.
I don't understand it.
You've always said that the person you fall in love with is your type.
I don't get it.
20 year old woman who wants to marry Oharu
I'm so happy!
Oh, my, oh, my, oh, my, oh, my, oh, my!
A 20-year-old girl wants to marry me.
What should I do?
You have to be kind.
Not just kindness.
It's not just about being kind, it's about being there when the time comes.
It's not just about being nice, it's about being really kind.
That's important, isn't it?
Anyway, I like someone who is kind and treats me well.
I know, I'm sure I'll be like that in the future.
I think I'm going to like someone who is kind to me and spoils me anyway.
Someone who can laugh with me when either of us laughs. I'm confident about this one, because I have this laugh.
I'm confident about this. Confident about what?
Someone with a kind personality I'm rooting for you, Oharu-chan.
What's this "I'm rooting for you, Oharu-chan"?
I'm rooting for you!
You look good with twintails.
Twintails look good on you.She looks great with twin tails.
She's a screw-up, hardworking and loves pink.
Someone like Natan is my type.
That's...
She's very idealistic.
Yeah, Natan's type is very idealistic.
I don't think you'll meet many like her.
I don't think you'll meet many of that type.
I don't think the Na-tan type is easy to find.
Na-tan is already at about 15 million points.
I don't think it's that hard to find.
I'll only marry a dog lover.
I think that's a good idea.
If he's left-handed, likes coffee, and is smart, I'll like him.
What's that?
That's like a requirement.
If he's left-handed, likes coffee, and is smart, I'll like him.
I don't get it.
My favorite type is Kanami Tsujino.
Kanami Tsujino for marriage
What do you look for in a girlfriend, Kanami Tsujino?
I'll make sure he knows that.
If you get infatuation with love, it's already your destiny!
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
It's kind of instinctive, isn't it?
I'm having a love stroke right now.
Then he's the one.
Hmmm...
If I'm going to get married, I want to marry a guy who has big eyes, likes ramen noodles, and looks good in pink.
What? Who do you mean?
Someone I can relax with. He's right next to me.
Someone I can relax with. What a boast!
Someone who is fun to be with. Someone who is also a member of the advertising department... or someone who has similar interests.
Oh, that's great!
I'd be happy to see couples who are members of the advertising department or married to other members of the advertising department.
Yum! It's good, but it's getting a little lukewarm.
I've always wanted to get married.
It's not too late! It's not too late! Come on! Go for it!
Face is important in a relationship, but when it comes to marriage, I want someone who's kind and responsible.
My mom used to look at my face a lot when we were dating, but when it comes to marriage, I don't think I should care about the face.
But when it comes to marriage, she doesn't care about the face anymore.
She said that since she's going to be with him for a long, long time, she can't look at his face anymore.
I want to marry Oharu-chanDon't you get many marriage proposals from college girls?
Petite girls.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Honest.
Honesty is good.
I'll marry someone nicer and cooler than you.
Hey, Daddy.
I'll marry someone nicer and cooler than you. Daddy!
I'm looking at you!
Dad!
Good luck, Daddy!
I like fun, simple people with culture.
Oh, wow!
A fun, simple person with culture.
What's he like? I don't know.
I don't know.
Is he formal?
Definitely not. What's he like? I don't know.
Definitely not.
I don't know.
If I'm going to marry someone, I'm definitely going to marry someone who's a healer, a warm-heart kind of guy.
Why? Is it to relax?
You want to relax?
I don't know.
I'd rather be married to someone who's...
Or someone who's loud.
I'd rather be around someone who's...
I guess I'm more comfortable with someone who's not so loud.
Well, I'm off.
Awww...
I'm off.
Well...
There's no end to the list.
In the end, the person I fell in love with was my type.
There it is again!
The person I fell in love with is my type.
Hmmm...
Someone who loves his family.Family oriented
Someone who chooses his words carefully.
Someone who chooses their words carefully.
Yeah, let's do our best.
Well... a family man.
Well, we're on the same page there.
The type of person I'd like and the type of person I'd actually like are polar opposites.
Really?
Wow!
What kind of person would that be, for example?
That's unusual.
It's not like you want to marry your guess anymore.
The one who naturally walks on the wrong side of the street when we're walking side by side.
I get told this a lot.
But you know what, I think it's pretty important.
Even if our anniversary or birthday falls on the same day as Jikken's concert...
Someone who understands me enough to let me go to the Tokugawa concert even if it conflicts with my anniversary or birthday.
Is this understanding?
This...
It's like someone who puts your hobbies first.
Someone who is a good match for you, that's for sure.
That's very true, yes.
Hello, from Indonesia.
Hello!
Indonesia
LOVE
love love love
this and that
this is unbelievable
unintentionally
this, this, this, this, this
Compota, no more
No more! Compota, no more!
Kompota, no!
I want to go out with Sunaki and get married!
Please do your best!
You can do it! I'm sure! She's only 18, right?
You can still do it!
I'm looking for a girl with a big forehead, mouth and thick chin.
There are no girls with big foreheads and mouths!
I'm sorry.
I'd be very happy to go to a live performance of Jikkyo Sensen and have a good time with you.
I've been practicing "settle fights within the day" since I was dating my husband, so maybe it's a sense of romance.
I like the second verse of that song.
After a fight, I always buy two ice creams
I'm captivated by the kindness of you who smiles at me and says, "I'm sorry.
I like this one.
I like it. I like that it's real life too.
Someone who doesn't deny what other people like. That's an absolute must.
Anyway, someone I can feel comfortable with and have fun with. Spy high school students.
Someone who is fun to be with. That's the most important thing, isn't it?
Someone who is patient. Someone who makes me feel safe.
I guess you're right.
Someone who's patient... even if it comes to marriage.
Someone who's patient and patient will probably be good in a marriage.
It's important to be patient when it comes to marriage.
It was fun to be with someone who shares the same sense of humor.
It's nice to be with someone who shares the same sense of humor.
We can laugh together.
Who doesn't like cucumbers?
Why? Why?
What do you mean?
Well, don't be too bossy with the waiter.
I'm the one who can say it.
I just said this.
I'm not at the age where marriage is a big deal. I'm not at an age where marriage is a big deal.
I'm not too old for marriage, but if he's happy with my presence, that's all that matters.
Does age matter? Marriage?
I don't think it has anything to do with it.
I don't know...
Personally, I don't think it matters, but... personally, I don't think it matters.
I don't care if you're very high up or very low down.
Personally...
A girl as energetic as Hachan! I'm happy! Cheerful! Yay!
I want a girl who is not afraid to go to cute cafes or
I want someone who will go with me to a cute café or a popular place.
huh?
That's a bit of a problem.
It depends on how cute she is, right? In a guy's opinion...
I don't know why I'm giving you a guy's opinion.
Someone with common sense.You're the one with common sense.
You're so cute.
Well, it would be ideal.
I'd like someone who'll watch over me while I'm pushing my idol.
That's why.
You say you're into idols, but...
I mean, it's my hobby.
So it's my hobby.
You can't be against a hobby.
It's not good to be negative about a hobby.
It's not a good thing to be negative about a hobby.
A person who can say "sorry" and "thank you
This is a given.
I want to be pampered by my older sister.
I think it's fine.
I think it's good.
It's good to be honest.
This is fun!
I want someone who's nice only to me! You're so cute! So cute!
Someone who can praise each other, compliment each other, tell each other what's wrong, and think about how to say it.
I think I'm still not good at this, so when there's something I can't do, I get angry at myself for not being able to do it.
When I can't do something, I get angry at myself for not being able to do it.
I get angry at myself for not being able to do something and become silent.
That happens a lot.
That's why I think I have to grow up a little more.
I think I need to grow up a little bit.
I'm thinking about it.
I'm thinking about it, but
But I can't improve on that.
That's why
I'd like to be able to do that a little more.
Someone who is kind and considerate
And someone who will help me when I need it.
These things are important, aren't they?
Someone who has the same interests as you.
Well, we have the same hobbies.
That's a tough one.
Someone who doesn't deny your hobbies is still good.
But when it comes to someone whose hobbies match, it's a little more difficult.
The people I've liked in the past...
The people I've liked so far are shy people.
I can tell when they open up to me while we're talking.
That makes me happy, and I find myself liking them.
They start talking to me, they change the way they call me...
Someone who will forgive me if I go to see Oharu-chan because I'm a selfish princess.
And over 170 tall... Suddenly I got a great one... Suddenly I got an absolute requirement.
I like people who are mocking and overreacting.
I like girls who laugh a lot.
That makes me happy.
He says he's happy and thinks it's him.
I'm sitting low.
Let's raise it.
I admire independent women, strong women, and women who are trying to create something.
I'm off, aren't I?
I like men who wear glasses.
Do you have glasses?
Men with glasses.
I don't have any glasses right now.
Men with glasses. What? Where are my glasses?
I used to have three pairs of Zatte glasses.
Glasses boys, I know what you mean.
I like guys with glasses, don't you?
Also, it's not fair that guys who don't usually wear glasses suddenly put them on.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
People who look you in the eye and talk to you.
I'm Oharu.
It's Oharu.
Someone who can throw up in the rain at night because I'm stubborn, and someone who won't be embarrassed to take me somewhere.
Someone who won't be embarrassed to take you anywhere.
This is...
It's a little bit minimal.
Finished [fast forward].
complete meal
[Fast forward]
I love it when a girl adds a rubber band to her mouth and it gets all moldy.
[fast forward]
Oh!Oh.
I don't have a rubber, so I won't do it.
[fast forward]
There's a rubber there, but I won't do it.
Someone like Hito-chan.
Oh, my God.
[fast forward]
Well, it has to be someone who loves me.
There's a bunch of cute girls in here.
What the hell?
They're cute.
I like boys in movies and dramas who get their heart broken.
The ones who stop being nice.
I totally understand
Haruna
I was watching a drama called "Kono Koe Won't You Warm Up?
I loved Kiki Mako in it.
I really loved Makocchan, but...
But she didn't get her comeuppance.
I'm second best. That kind of guy is great.
I really do.
So, please...
Even if he's the one you're going out with now, I hope he'll come back in the end.
My type is a woman like Nadeshiko Yamato.
What kind of person?
Someone with pretty eyes and always smiling, like Yuri.
I've got two of these, and they're quite a lot.
That's quite a lot.
Someone who gets along well with my family.
This is important.
I have a lot of family too.
Including relatives.
But I think it's very important to have people who get along with you.
I think it's very important.
I'm not good at talking, so someone who talks to me all the time.
On the contrary.
I'm not sure if that's true for me.
I don't know.
I guess I am.
I'm childish.
I'm attracted to people who think like adults.
It's a world I don't know.
That's...
If I'm going to marry, I definitely want a man who can cook.
It's the best way to get a hold of a man's stomach.
If it's a daughter, I'd definitely want a man who can cook, because it's the best way to get into someone's pants.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
You know, my mom told me something...
She said something about marrying a chef.
She said something about marrying a cook.
I don't cook enough.
But then she told me that cooks don't cook at home.
So she wants a man who really likes to cook.
Not a chef.
Because cooks cook for a living.
They do it for a living.
They don't cook at home much.
I see.
But that doesn't really mean anything.
I don't really have any data on that.
I want someone who likes to fold her arms.
He's cute.
I often walk arm-in-arm with my mom.
I often walk around arm-in-arm with my mom.
That's cute.
She's so cute, I got a little upset.
I'm just a little bit upset.
You have a beautiful way of eating noodles.
Am I beautiful? The way you eat noodles.
People reading books at the edge of the classroom
Cute! Cute!
Someone my own age or older who understands me.
You don't like younger people
Someone who smiles like Haru-chan
It makes me smile too.
Is that a compliment? It's a compliment.
It says "people who laugh a lot.
That's a compliment.You're complimenting me.
When I ask you to pick up a tissue, you look at the situation and make a judgment call.
I want to marry someone who can judge the situation and pick up a tissue appropriately.
There are several ways to pick up a tissue.
There are different ways to pick up a tissue.
I want you to think of me first.
Of course you do.
I totally understand.
I like funny people.
Someone who makes me laugh a lot.
That makes me happy.
I'm thinking like an "I-song" and a "selfish princess".
I'm like a selfish princess.
A little heavy?
I'd like to know what you're thinking.
I want to know about Hachitaro's.
Hachitaro's?
What?
What do you look for in a girlfriend?
Like an absolute requirement.
Like the type of person you like?
The type of person you like?
I don't know.
The type of person you like.
I wonder.
Well, one who's kind.
Gentle? Boring.
I like people who are kind.
Well... what I mean by kindness is...
I'm a selfish princess type girl, but...
But... when you said something like... you know... like, "Can you get me a tissue right now?
When you ask me to take something away...
I'm really selfish.
I'm the kind of person who, instead of asking her to pick something up, I'd give her a signal with my eyes, like my little sister or something.
I wonder if there is someone who understands that.
Also, I say this a lot when I talk about my dreams, but I think girls want people to sympathize with them.
That's why I want them to say, "You're doing great!
Understand?
Tell me you understand.
I want them to say, "You're doing great.
I want someone who tells me I'm doing great.
Okay. Something like that.
And lately...
I tend to be a paper driver.
I'd like someone who can drive.
Yes.
Also, someone who can carry on a conversation.
When we're having dinner together.
Someone who is easy to talk to when we have dinner together.
Yes.
And someone who gets angry with you.
Oh my God, oh my God, oh my God, oh my God, oh my God!
My bad side comes out.
I want to talk about love with Oharu.
Can we do it at a talk session?
What? If it's something I can do, sure.
If I'm going to date, I want someone who lives alone.
It's hard for working adults to live at home.
Don't say that.
I'm doing my best, and so are the guys.
They forgive me if I suddenly start singing in my life. who will no longer sing along with me.
I do this a lot.
Someone who will be by my side for the rest of my life. That's nice.
A boyfriend. Someone who understands Oharu-chan.
Can you meet him? I'm happy, but can you meet him? This.
What are you looking for in a boyfriend? Mani Oharu You seem a little heavy-handed, but why am I... why am I acting like a heavy-handed character from last time?
I don't know why, I don't know why.
I love you
I love you!
Can you wink at me?
Can you do it? Can you do it?
It would have been so much fun if there was a corn on the cob, but there wasn't.
People who have hobbies and enjoy doing the same thing.
I like people who can forgive me for supporting idols of the opposite sex.
Yeah.
That's what's important... idol fans.
I've been married for 5 years, and my favorite type is my husband.
He's considerate, cares about his family, and spoils me.
That's really nice.
He's so good! He's the best!
He's more cute than beautiful.Cute girls are more my type than beautiful girls.
Ah! I've been waiting for that!
Good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good.
Someone who wants to go with me when I tell him I'm going to Tokikuri for Christmas.
Oh, that's nice.
Someone who's there for you when you're happy or sad.
I think that's really important.
That's what I'm thinking too.
Yes, I agree.
I like people who eat food like it's delicious.
Yes, I like this too.
Someone who forgives me for buying a lot of sneakers
What do you mean... well, this is one thing... someone who will forgive me if I buy a lot of sneakers.
This is one hobby, isn't it?
I keep saying "someone who gets excited with me when I play Kurazushi's Bikurapon.
It's nice... someone who doesn't forget his childishness.
It's nice to have someone who shares your sense of humor.
It's important to have a good sense of humor, isn't it?
Someone who doesn't interfere too much.
I think that's true.
Someone I can truly enjoy spending time with.
That's why I'm asking what kind of man you're looking for.
If I'm going to marry, someone who's also kind. My current boyfriend would be ideal.
What?
My ideals are so high that I can see myself being single for the rest of my life.
I'm 19 now.
You'll be fine at 19.
Why? Why? Why are your ideals so high?
Someone who won't just take you at your word and leave when you're sulking.
Someone who won't let go of your hand and stay by your side.
I know what you mean.
Girls don't like to be left alone when they're down or sulking.
They don't like to be left alone when they're depressed or sulking.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
I'm going to take the liberty of saying so myself.
I don't like to be left alone.
That's why.
That's what it's all about.
A pat on the head, a back rub, something like that.
Like, "I understand.
Empathy... empathy.
I like you, Ha-chan.
She told me! Thank you.
I get a kick out of guys who are taller than me.
That's true.
I prefer tall people too.
Or shorter.
I mean, they're cute, but...
I'd rather have a tall guy.
Someone who's fun to be with.
Someone who cares about himself and me
I don't know, I feel like he cares too much.
I'd rather have someone who cares about me and me only than someone who only cares about himself.
I admire someone who cares about me but also cares about himself.
A kind person
In the end, it all comes back to that.
So, how many did you write this time?
You wrote 4976 comments!
Thank you very much.
It was interesting to hear about everyone's favorite type.
I'd like to do this kind of thing again.
I was very happy to know that.
Thank you very much!
That's why I liked this video so much,
I couldn't say it out loud even though I'm this type of person,
I'm going to say it in the comment section! If you liked this video, or if you have any other comments, please leave them in the comment section!
I'd love to hear from you! So, please give me a good button and a high rating!
Good button and high rating are the same.
Please click the "Good" button and subscribe to our channel!
I'm practicing for the live guitar distribution when I reach 10,000 subscribers, so please subscribe to my channel and tell your friends about it!
See you in the next video!
bye-bye!